# Aneta Srbinovska

070-717-400 anetasrbinovska7@gmail.com Dimche Lahchanski 17/7 7000 Bitola

## **Profile**

I am a sales and customer service professional with extensive leadership experience in the retail industry. My goal is to make use of my excellent communication and organizational skills to make a significant contribution to the success of the company.

# Experience

**CUSTOMER SERVICE SPECIALIST, STAPLES; ROCHESTER, NY - 2007-2016** 

Responsible for providing supervision to all areas of the store. Had an active role in maximizing sales and ensuring complete customer satisfaction. Was able to assess and evaluate direct reports, and take a lead role in providing guidance, training and coaching on company initiatives, sales programs and product knowledge to maximize sales and earnings. Other responsibilities included but were not limited to:

- Partnering with management to set sales goals and targets. Ensure team understands connection between store financial success and bonus programs.
- Responsible for closing and opening of the store.
- Maximize sales opportunities by leveraging the sales capabilities of associates by using current selling techniques and company programs.
- Accountable for the prevention and resolution of customer issues by ensuring a high level of customer service is provided by associates.
- Model, promote and partner with management to hold others accountable for customer service excellence in the Services departments.
- Partner with management to oversee coordination and execution of services and maximize department productivity.
- Responsible to execute, communicate and ensure understanding of flyer or promotional items.
- Participated in the recruitment, hiring and onboarding processes for the services departments.

- Responsible for counting the safe, preparing and making daily bank deposits, completing paperwork and keypunching cashier totals on a daily basis.
- Maintaining and sustaining an efficient filing system for all relevant paperwork as per company standards.
- Accountable to maintain the day to day operation of the Cash on Delivery (C.O.D) process including reporting, transactions, payments and collections as per company policy.
- Monitor adequate inventory levels and places orders for all register and related supplies.
- Tracking all cash over/shorts, communicating results to management and follow up with associates.
- Monitor and investigate cashier infractions, merchandise and copy cards, phone cards, price overrides, count integrity and lease transactions.

#### OFFICE SUPPLY ASSOCIATE, STAPLES; ROCHESTER, NY - 2006-2007

Responsible for providing exceptional customer service and creating a customer centric environment. Tasks and responsibilities included but were not limited to:

- Ordering merchandise from vendors, receiving deliveries from suppliers, and maintaining inventory records
- Keeping shelves stocked with products by stocking shelves and pushing inventory to the end caps or ends of aisles
- Taking inventory of all items on store shelves and recording information about items such as style number and size
- Help customers find products using the store's computerized inventory system
- Updating inventory levels in the computer system to reflect new inventory levels
- Recommending new products based on customer preferences and interests
- Processing cash and CC sales at counter
- Processing returns and exchanges, including scanning barcodes and entering data into the computer system
- Assisting customers with locating specific items or departments within stores
- Demonstrating products to customers and providing them with information about how to use the product effectively

#### STOE ASSOCIATE, TOPS; ROCHESTER, NY - 2005-2006

Bakery Clerk - Offering customers fresh-baked breads, rolls, cookies, muffins, and donuts and preparing the cakes and pies. Responsibilities included:

- Providing friendly and attentive customer service
- Slicing, pricing, and packaging product
- Maintaining proper shelf/display conditions through cleaning, straightening, and rotating products
- Taking customer orders accurately for cakes or other specialty items as needed
- Ensuring proper handling and storing of product

Cashier/Front End - As a cashier I was in the unique position of being the final point of contact with our customers, and have the opportunity to leave a lasting impression by providing friendly and courteous service by accurately and efficiently checking out customers' orders. Responsibilities included:

- Providing friendly and attentive customer service
- Scanning and/or ringing customers' purchases
- Bagging customer orders
- Collecting payment for customer transactions
- Stocking supplies in the immediate area, returning shopbacks, retrieving carts, and miscellaneous cleaning and straightening of various shelf sections as needed
- Directing customers to an appropriate manager when necessary

# Education

Faculty of Tourism and Hospitality - Ohrid

### Skills

- Leadership
- Management
- Problem-solving
- Customer Service
- Sales
- Time Management